

CONTACT ME AT

- Address: #106, Sumedha residential enclave. Ankadakatte, Koteshwara 576222
- shettydhanush13@gmail.com
- my portfolio
- in <u>@dhanush-s-shetty</u>

SKILLS

- Js javaScript
- (S) Node.js
- 🦃 React
- ♦ MongoDB
- **Elasticsearch**
- 5 HTML
- 3 CSS
- aws Amazon Web Services
- Mocha chai
- ◆ Git
- **3** D3.js

EDUCATION

University Visvesvaraya College of Engineering

BE | Aug 2013 - Jun 2017

• Grade: First Class Distinction

DHANUSH S SHETTY

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Experienced Interface Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the design industry. Skilled in React, Node.js, JavaScript, SQL/NoSQL database and AWS. Information technology professional with a Bachelor of Engineering from University Vishweshwaraya College of Engineering. Travelling or cooking while not coding.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-stack Developer

Piktorlabs | JAN 2019 - Present

- Built UI and backend-services for <u>uniqlo</u> ecommerce website ecosystem with catalogue, inventory, user and order management services using microservices architecture.
- Increased mobile users 2x by revamping UI with a robust mobile first approach using React, Node.js and MongoDB.
- Optimized search time by 300% by remodelling the RESTful services in Node.js and Elasticsearch.
- Enhanced user experience and accomplished web page objectives by creating site structure, navigation, search engine optimization and graphic animations.
- Fixed bugs and refined overall code quality which significantly improved user experience and development time.
- Technologies: Node.js, React, MongoDB, AWS, Elasticsearch.

Frontend Developer

Moonraft Innovation Labs | Aug 2017 - Jan 2019

- Developed pixel perfect responsive and modular web pages using Angular 7 and React.
- Implemented RESTful services in Node.js, AWS (API gateway, DynamoDB) with UI integration and Iterated user experience to increase user's form completion in Jazz by 200%.
- Performed unit testing for front-end and back-end services to identify bugs and UI improvements using Mocha and Jest.
- Managed the training program for newly recruited employees.
- Technologies: Angular, React, Node.js, D3.js, MongoDB.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Single-handedly built the entire travel booking ecosystem called <u>trippospace</u>. which curates trips from handpicked travel agents to ease the booking hassle for travellers.
- Built a platform called <u>skillospace</u> where one can learn beginner level pass time skills.